She's stepping out into the world.
Barefoot is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Andrew Fleming.
The "black sheep" son of a wealthy family meets a young psychiatric
patient who's been raised in isolation her entire life.
He takes the naive young woman home for his brother's wedding an improbable romance
blooms, as she impresses everyone with her genuine, simple charms.
Daisy, played by Evan Rachel Wood.
Jay Wheeler, played by Scott Speedman.
Dr. Bertleman, played by J.K. Simmons.
Jason Wheeler, played by Treat Williams.
Mrs. Wheeler, played by Kate Burton.
Kate Benet, played by Andrea Moore.
Barefoot is a 2014 American romantic comedy film directed by Andrew
Fleming and distributed by Roadside Attractions.
It was written by Stephen Zotnowski and is technically a "remake" of the 2005 German film Barfuss despite the
fact that Barfuss was itself based on Zotnowski's original story and screenplay "Barefoot".
It stars Evan Rachel Wood, Scott Speedman, Treat Williams, Kate Burton and J.
The story follows Jay Wheeler, the son of a wealthy family who meets Daisy, a psychiatric
patient who was raised in isolation, as he takes her home for his brother's wedding.
The film was produced by WhiteFlame Productions and premiered at the Santa
Barbara International Film Festival on February 2, 2014.
It received a limited theatrical release and was simultaneously
released to Video on demand on February 21, 2014.
It grossed a total of $15,071.
It received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of naivety, remake,
psychiatric hospital, naive, family.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.